// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The universe is estimated to be between ten and twenty billion years old. This estimate is based on the value of which constant?",
    answer: "The Hubble Constant",
    options: [
      "The mass of the Earth",
      "The speed of light",
      "The Hubble Constant",
      "The mass of the electron"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following first hypothesized that the Earth orbited the sun?",
    answer: "Copernicus",
    options: [
      "Alexander the Great",
      "Copernicus",
      "Socrates",
      "Tycho Brahe"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The LAST manned moon flight was made in what year?",
    answer: "1972",
    options: [
      "1971",
      "1972",
      "1973",
      "1974"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The cosmic background radiation, a remnant of the Big Bang, is at what temperature?",
    answer: "2.7K",
    options: [
      "100K",
      "0K",
      "5.3K",
      "2.7K"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A planet is said to be at aphelion when it is:",
    answer: "farthest from the sun",
    options: [
      "closest to the sun",
      "farthest from the sun",
      "at it's highest point above the ecliptic",
      "at it's lowest point below the ecliptic"
    ]
  },
  
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "At any time we may describe the position of an inferior planet by the angle it makes with the sun as seen from the earth. This angle is called the :",
     answer: "elongation",
    options: [
       "ecliptic",
       "epicycle",
       "elongation",
       "proxima"
     ]
   },
   
   {
      numb: 7,
     question: "Which of the following planets has the greatest eccentricity?",
     answer: "Pluto",
    options: [
       "Pluto",
       "Jupiter",
       "Mars",
       "Mercury"
     ]
   },
   { numb: 8,
     question: "On which of the following planets would the sun rise in the west?",
     answer: "Venus",
    options: [
       "Saturn",
       "Pluto",
       "Mercury",
       "Venus"
     ]
   },
   {
   numb: 9,
     question: "Which planet seems to be turned on its side with an axis tilt of 98 degrees?",
     answer: "Uranus",
    options: [
       "Uranus",
       "Pluto",
       "Neptune",
       "Saturn"
     ]
   },
   {
   numb: 10,
     question: "The angle that the full moon takes up in the night sky is equal to which of the following values?",
     answer: "1/2 degrees",
    options: [
       "1/8 degree",
       "1/2 degrees",
       "1 degree",
       "2 degrees"
     ]
   },
];